<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Wordoko</title>
 <link href="http://wordoko.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://wordoko.com/"/>
 <updated>2014-09-29T10:12:35-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://wordoko.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Juan Lazo</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Learning Japanese: The Four Alphabets</title>
   <link href="http://wordoko.com/blog/learning-japanese-the-four-alphabets"/>
   <updated>2014-09-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://wordoko.com/blog/learning-japanese-the-four-alphabets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Leanrning Japanese&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that there are &lt;em&gt;four&lt;/em&gt; alphabets used for Japanese? Some people are might say that they’re not alphabets, they’re &lt;em&gt;syllabaries&lt;/em&gt;. For our purposes, lets call them alphabets. They are:
-&lt;strong&gt;Hiragana&lt;/strong&gt;
-&lt;strong&gt;Katakana&lt;/strong&gt;
-&lt;strong&gt;Kanji&lt;/strong&gt;
-&lt;strong&gt;Romanji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Romanji&lt;/strong&gt; is the easiest. You most likely already know it because it you’re reading this post. It’s the same alphabet used for English. 
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kanji&lt;/strong&gt; is seen by many as the most difficult alphabet to learn. It’s based on Chinese characters and it’s not syllabic, meaning that each character doesn’t represent a syllable the way that the Roman alphabet does. Instead it’s an alphabet of logograms meaning that each character represents a word (all kinds of words from nouns to adjectives to verbs and things in between). The interesting thing is that you can combine two ideas together to make a new idea. For example the kanji for “electricity” and “car” combine to form the kanji for “train”. 
&lt;/br&gt;
The final two are grouped together; they’re called &lt;strong&gt;Kana&lt;/strong&gt; when they’re grouped together and separately they are two alphabets known as &lt;strong&gt;Hiragana&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Katakana&lt;/strong&gt;.
These two alphabets are generally used for different things. Hiragana is used for grammatical particles (infinitives and negators) as well as words that are originially Japanese. Katakana is generally used for foreign loan words, as well as proper names that can’t be written in Kanji.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
